Guide to the Stanford News Service Audiovisual Recordings SC1125
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videorecordings, 1936-2011; Series 2
  - Joe Manning, associate professor of classics, discusses Stanford’s acquisition of Erichsen library of Egyptology, 2007-10-23; 07-1023-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Joe Manning, associate professor of classics, discusses Stanford’s acquisition of Wolja Erichsen’s Egyptology library and shows books from the collection; Coptic texts; Erichsen’s personal annotated copy of demotic dictionary; marriage contract; land sale contract; photographs of now-lost papyri
  - Falling atoms: Kasevich, Dimopoulos, Hogan, 2007-10-24; 07-1024-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    "interviews with Mark Kasevich, professor of physics; Jason Hogan, graduate researcher; and Savas Dimopoulos, professor of physics, explaining their plan to test Einstein’s equivalence principle by measuring falling atoms in a special tube basement of Varian building"
  - First Nations/ Hopkins, 2007-10-29; 07-1029-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Fellows of the First Nations' Futures Program came from New Zealand and Hawaii for a two-week session sponsored by the Woods Institute at Hopkins Marine Station. Footage contains Steve Palumbi, professor of biology, and Aulani Wilhelm Morton, Superintendent, papahanaumokuakea Marine National Monument. There is a short documentary.
  - First Nations Interviews (3) Short B-Roll, 2007-10-29; 07-1029-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    "Fellows of the First Nations' Futures Program came from New Zealand and Hawaii for a two-week session sponsored by the Woods Institute at Hopkins Marine Station. First interview is Noelani Lee (Hawaii). Second is Gerard te Heuheu (Aotearoa / New Zealand) - [Maori]. Third is Mawae Morton. Fourth interview is Peter Vitouser."
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL) Goodbye, 2007-10-31; 07-1031-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    "Hansen Experimental Physics Laboratory (HEPL) Goodbye (pre-demolition footage; demolition began Jan. 29.2008)"
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL) Goodbye, 2007-10-31; 07-1031-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
  - Embracing Diversity at McCaw Hall, 2007-11-01 (Box 46)
  - Junior robotic car places second in Defense Department competition in Victorville, California., 2007-11-03; 07-1103-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Junior robotic car finishing second in Defense Department competition in Victorville, California. Stanford Racing Team. DARPA. Features Sebastian Thrun, race team leader and professor of computer science and of electrical engineering.
  - Junior robotic car places second in Defense Department competition in Victorville, California., 2007-11-03; 07-1103-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
  - Stanford Symphony playing at Quad, 2007-11-04; 07-1104-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    The Stanford Symphony playing Beethoven and Mozart at the Quad.
  - Stanford Symphony playing at Quad, 2007-11-04; 07-1104-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    The Stanford Symphony playing Mozart at the Quad.
  - Press conference at Stanford after Junior robotic car placed second in Defense Department competition., 2007-11-05; 07-1105-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Press conference at Stanford after Junior robotic car placed second in Defense Department competition on Nov. 3, 2007; Sebastian Thrun, race team leader and professor of computer science and of electrical engineering, speaks and shows award medal; Mike Montemerlo, senior research engineer, speaks.
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL) Party, 2007-11-05; 07-1105-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Pre-demolition Party for the Hansen Experimental Physics Laboratory building. Built in 1947, it was the site of Stanford's first linear accelerator.
  - Theater director JoAnne Akalaitis visits Stanford to workshop her new production of Euripides’ The Bacchae, 2007-11-08; 07-1108-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Theater director JoAnne Akalaitis visits Stanford to workshop her new production of Euripides’ The Bacchae. Interview with Akalaitis; rehearsals
  - How to Listen - M. Applebaum, 2007-11-08 (Box 46)
  - Mark D's Radio Show "The Slippedy Doo Da", 2007-11-09 (Box 46)
  - Spelman College’s SpelBots, the nation’s only all-female, African-American competitive student robotics team, visited campus., 2007-11-13; 07-1113-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Spelman College’s SpelBots, the nation’s only all-female, African-American competitive student robotics team, visited campus. Courtyard of Clark Center. Eric Roberts, professor of computer science, interviewed.
  - BeWell and Stanford health initiative kicks off with free lunch, 2007-11-14; 07-1114-01; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    BeWell@Stanford health initiative kicks off with free lunch: Eric Stein, senior associate athletic director; Rafi Taherian, executive director of Stanford Dining; Marcella Stauber, admin. at Physical Wellness Office; staff handing out meals; people signing up for the program on laptops; people showing lunch offerings
  - Shelley Fisher Fishkin, professor of English, discusses long-lost Mark Twain play, 2007-11-15; 07-1115-01; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Interview with Shelley Fisher Fishkin, professor of English. She discusses the long-lost Mark Twain play, “Is He Dead Yet”, that she found while doing research, and its relationship to Twain's life and oeuvre.
  - Margo Gerritsen, assistant professor of energy resources and engineering, discusses her Smart Energy Show blog, 2007-11-27; 07-1127-1 (Box 53)
    Margo Gerritsen, assistant professor of energy resources and engineering, discusses her Smart Energy Show blog
  - Army High-Performance Computing Research Center ceremony, 2007-11-29; 07-1129-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Campus ceremony celebrated start of the Army High-Performance Computing Research Center, a consortium of four universities and NASA. President Hennessy, Rabbi Patricia Karlin-Neumann and the Rev. Scotty McLennan were among those at the ceremony.
  - Army High-Performance Computing Research Center ceremony, 2007-11-29; 07-1129-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Laboratory (HEPL) exteriors, 2007-12-04; 07-1204-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Hansen Experimental Physics Laboratory (HEPL) exteriors; taped to record building exteriors before HEPL was demolished in January 2008
  - Clay Carson, 2007-12-04; 1851; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 45)
  - Demo of innovative furniture and offices at Porter Drive office complex in Stanford Research Park, 2007-12-18; 07-1218-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Demo of innovative furniture and offices at 3145 Porter Drive office complex in Stanford Research Park, which will house about 300 staff members.
  - Mark Jacobson, 2007-12-20; 07-1220-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Interview with Mark Jacobson, professor of civil and environmental engineering. He had released a study showing direct links between an increase in carbon dioxide emissions and an increase in resulting deaths, a particularly relevant finding in light of the December of 2007 decision by the EPA denying California and other states the right to set their own limits on carbon dioxide emissions.
  - Precourt Institute for Energy Press Conference, A Cam, 2008-01-12; 09-0112-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Stanford President John Hennessy held a news conference at Memorial Auditorium to lay out plans for the new Precourt Institute for Energy. The $100 million in new funds will enable the hiring of additional faculty and support new graduate students, in addition to the more than $30 million in yearly funding now spent on energy research.
  - Precourt Institute for Energy Press Conference, B Cam, Cutaways, 2008-01-12; 09-0112-3; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
  - Sam Wineburg- Famous Americans Study, 2008-01-22; 08-0122-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Interview with Sam Wineburg, a professor of education. He created survey of 2000 high school students and 2000 adults about America’s Greatest Heroes. When the high school students across the United States were asked this question—excluding presidents and presidents' wives—Martin Luther King Jr., Rosa Parks and Harriet Tubman headed the list.
  - SussKind Lect - 1 of 2, 2008-01-28; 2170; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 47)
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL) demolition, 2008-01-30; 08-0130-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL) demolition
  - Woods Institute Energy Seminars, 2008-01-30 (Box 46)
  - Cagan Sekercioglu, senior research scientist in biological sciences, discusses effect of climate change on bird populations, extinctions., 2008-01-31; 08-0131-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Cagan Sekercioglu, senior research scientist in biological sciences, discusses effect of climate change on bird populations, extinctions.
  - Hari Manoharan, assistant professor of physics, discusses quantum drums., 2008-02-05; 08-0205-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Hari Manoharan, Stanford assistant professor of physics, uses a scanning tunneling microscope to build tiny nano-structures in the shape of drums, with special quantum properties. His work has implications for quantum mechanics and chip design. Also featured: Chris Moon, graduate researcher.
  - Voting at Stanford on Super Tuesday (presidential primary), 2008-02-05; 08-0205-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Stanford voters were out in droves Feb. 5, Super Tuesday, to cast their ballots at polling place in Escondido Village. Voters waiting in line. Features: Doug Karlson, Santa Clara County poll worker; Hannah Krakauer, ‘10, first-time voter
  - Claude Steele at Center for Advanced Studies in the Behavioral Sciences, 2008-02-11; 08-0211-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    Claude Steele, professor of psychology and director of the Center for Advanced Study (CASBS) in the Behavioral Sciences, discusses CASBS-Stanford partnership; CASBS became part of Stanford effective Jan. 1, 2008
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2) exteriors, 2008-02-12; 08-0212-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): exteriors"
  - Barbara Slavin, 2008-02-12; MP3 file (Box 46)
  - The Music Emily Heard (and played) Campbell Recital Hall, 2008-02-13 (Box 46)
  - Tour of California Bicycle Race: Racers; B-Roll, 2008-02-17; 08-0217-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    "Tour of California Bicycle Race: Racers; B-Roll The Amgen Tour of California kicked off its seven-day tour with a time trail competition which started at Palo Alto City Hall and ended on Palm Drive."
  - Tour of California Bicycle Race: Awards, 2008-02-17; 08-0217-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    "Tour of California Bicycle Race: Awards The Amgen Tour of California kicked off its seven-day tour with a time trail competition which started at Palo Alto City Hall and ended on Palm Drive."
  - Rick Shaw, dean of admission and financial aid, discusses enhanced financial aid program, 2008-02-20; 08-0220-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Rick Shaw, dean of undergraduate admission and financial aid, discusses enhanced financial aid program, under which parents with incomes of less than $100,000 will no longer pay tuition. press conference.
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2) tour, 2008-02-22; 08-0222-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): tour led by architect Tom Bauer"
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2): labs; interviews; circle room; plasma screens; exteriors, 2008-02-26; 08-0226-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): labs; interviews; circle room; plasma screens; exteriors"
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2): Koseff; atrium; meeting room; B-roll, 2008-02-27; 08-0227-1 (Box 50)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): interview with Jeff Koseff; atrium; meeting room; B-roll"
  - Sarah C. Heilshorn Materials to Heal and Rebuild the Human Body at Hewlett 200, 2008-02-28 (Box 46)
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2): letters spelling building name applied; screens, 2008-03-03; 08-0303-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): worker applies letters to side of building to spell out building name; sign; screens"
  - Yang Yamazaki Environmental Engineering Building (Y2E2) dedication, 2008-03-04; 08-0304-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    "Jerry Yang and Akiko Yamazaki Environment and Energy Building (Y2E2): dedication speakers include: President John Hennessy; donors and alumni Akiko Yamazaki and Jerry Yang interviews include: Jerry Yang"
  - Henry Paulson, 2008-03-08; 08-0308-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    U.S. Treasury Secretary Henry M. Paulson Jr. hiked and chatted with students Friday at sunrise at Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve. That evening, he delivered the keynote address at the 2008 Stanford Institute for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR) Economic Summit.
  - Roble Gym Studio, 2008-03-11 (Box 46)
  - Uncommon Knowledge - George Schultz, 2008-03-14 (Box 46)
  - OSO Teacher Program at School of Engineering, 2008-03-28 (Box 46)
  - Uncommon Knowledge - Henry Kissinger, 2008-04-03 (Box 46)
  - D. Lieberman Carnochan Lecture, 2008-04-04; MP3 file (Box 46)
  - Cubberly Lecture, 2008-04-07; WAV file (Box 46)
  - Marina Warnor, 2008-04-14; MP3 file (Box 46)
  - SLS Bov - State of the Legal Profession, 2008-04-18 (Box 46)
  - Sandra Day O’Connor Speech SD Only, 2008-04-22; 08-0422-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Sandra Day O'Connor, the first Rathbun Visiting Fellow, delivered the inaugural "Harry's Last Lecture on a Meaningful Life" talk at Memorial Church. She then answered questions from students about their future, the complexities of modern society and how a judge who believes in God should behave on the bench, among others.
  - Sandra Day O’Connor Q & A SD Only, 2008-04-22; 08-0422-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
  - Iranian Studies, 2008-04-22; MP3 file (Box 46)
  - Admit Weekend Thurs, 2008-04-24; 08-0424-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Prospective freshmen and their parents came to campus April 24 for three days of seminars, meetings, tours and dining designed to give them a closer look at the university and student life. On Thursday, they were greeted in White Plaza by students operating booths for various activities and organizations.
  - Johnny Dawkins, 2008-04-28; 08-0428-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Press Conference announcing that Johnny Dawkins had been named the new head coach of men's basketball at Stanford. Dawkins said it took him about 10 minutes to accept the offer from Director of Athletics Bob Bowlsby, shown with Dawkins.
  - Hewlett 200 #081528-1 Brainstorms - Brian Wandell Continuing studies, 2008-04-29 (Box 46)
  - Clifford Nass Drive Simulator, 2008-05-01; 08-0501-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    "Interview with Professor Clifford Nass, Communication and Sociology, at the Communication Between Humans and Interactive Media Lab. Nass, doctoral student Helen Harris, and undergraduates Kyle Davis, David Diaz and Brooke Sullivan searched for ways to help people control their emotions in the car in a study called ""Car-tharsis."
  - Wellness Fair, 2008-05-01; 08-0501-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Wellness Fair at the Arrillaga Center for Sports and Recreation with events including everything from rock climbing to bone-density tests. The fair was part of BeWell@Stanford, the university's ongoing wellness initiative.
  - Paul Wender AIDS, 2008-05-02; 08-0502-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Interview with Professor of Chemistry, Paul Wender. He has found a way to make a better “bird dog” to flush HIV out of the cells where it hides. His work is based on a compound from the Mamala plant, found in the Samoan rainforest.
  - Peter Michelson, 2008-05-02; 08-0502-3; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Stanford’s Peter Michelson is the principal investigator for the Gamma Ray Large Area Space Telescope (GLAST), launched by NASA on June 11, 2008. The orbiting observatory will study the gamma rays emitted by enormously powerful gamma-ray bursts, as well as pulses of energy from spinning neutron stars and strange beams of charged particles ejected from spinning black holes.
  - Quakers Boots, 2008-05-02; 08-0502-4; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Stanford Quakers sponsored an exhibit of boots on the ground, representing Californians who have died in Iraq near White Plaza called “Eyes Wide Open.” The exhibit also displayed shoes representing Iraqi civilians who been killed. The exhibit was created by the American Friends Service Committee, which was founded by Quakers in 1917 to provide conscientious objectors with an opportunity to aid civilian war victims.
  - Biosciences Diversity Symposium by Tyrone Hayes, 2008-05-05 (Box 46)
  - 2008 Community Partnership Award and Miriam Aaron Roland Volunteer Service Prize, 2008-05-07; 08-0507-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    The Office of Public Affairs, as part of an annual private luncheon being held today, presented the 2008 Community Partnership Awards to the Boys and Girls Clubs of the Peninsula, the Eastside School Field Studies class and the Hope House Scholars Program. The Haas Center for Public Service presented the 2008 Miriam Aaron Roland Volunteer Service Prize to Dr. Lars Osterberg. He told the Garden Court Hotel audience that the measure of a society is how it cares for the poor.
  - 37th Annual Powwow, 2008-05-09; 08-0509-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    37th Annual Stanford Powwow in Eucalyptus Grove. The three-day event, the largest student-run powwow in the country, included more than 20 dance competitions for men, women, boys and girls in categories such as the jingle dress dance, grass dance and fancy shawl dance.
  - 2008 Amy Blue Podium Cam, 2008-05-14; 08-0514-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Friends, relatives, faculty and staff attend the 2008 Amy Blue Awards ceremony at Lagunita Court. Winning that year were Mary Nolan, grounds supervisor in Grounds Services; Deana Fabbro-Johnston, associate director of the Earth Systems Program and Mary Morrison, director of funds management in the Financial Aid Office.
  - 2008 Amy Blue Cutaway Cam, 2008-05-14; 08-0514-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
  - Academic Council Panel Cubberley Auditorium, 2008-05-15; 08-0515-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    A panel of top administrators from across campus met in front of the academic council to discuss their perspectives on the goals for building a 21st-century campus. The panelists included President Hennessy, Ann Arvin, vice provost and dean of research; David Kreps, senior associate dean for academic affairs at the Graduate School of Business; David Lenox, university architect and director of campus planning; and Joseph Stagner, executive director of sustainability and energy management—Stanford’s first.
  - Academic Council Hennessy Building Speech, 2008-05-15; 08-0515-2; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    "AIn an address to the Academic Council, President John Hennessy reviewed the university’s accomplishments over the past year and spoke of Stanford’s goals in building a campus for the 21st century—namely, constructing state-of-the-art research and residential facilities, continuing to make sustainability a priority and employing responsible land-use practices. In addition, Hennessy emphasized the importance of adhering to the original campus plan by the famed landscape architect Frederick Law Olmsted."
  - Hennessy Academic Council Cutaways, 2008-05-15; 08-0515-3; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    "In an address to the Academic Council, President John Hennessy reviewed the university’s accomplishments over the past year and spoke of Stanford’s goals in building a campus for the 21st century—namely, constructing state-of-the-art research and residential facilities, continuing to make sustainability a priority and employing responsible land-use practices. In addition, Hennessy emphasized the importance of adhering to the original campus plan by the famed landscape architect Frederick Law Olmsted."
  - Malcolm Margolin Continuing Studies, 2008-05-15 (Box 46)
  - China Memorial Memorial Church, 2008-05-19; 08-0519-1a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Chinese students at Memorial Church pray for victims of the earthquake that struck Sichuan province in China. The service ended with a lighting of candles by a large congregation of Chinese students and scholars.
  - China Memorial Memorial Church, 2008-05-19; 08-0519-1b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
  - Roz Naylor, 2008-05-20; 08-0520-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Roz Naylor, director for the Program on Food Security and Environment summarizes why there is a worldwide food crisis, its causes, and why the U.S. needs to be the leader in solving the problem.
  - Springfest 2008, 2008-05-22; 08-0522-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    The annual Multicultural Springfest, which celebrates the diversity of Stanford’s non-faculty employees, also featured staff art and photography, live music, dance, spoken-word poetry, raffle prizes and lots of free food.Organizers estimate that about 5,000 Stanford staff showed up for music and great food at the 14th Annual Multicultural Springfest, staged this year at Frost Amphitheater.
  - Prius with PANDA system to create noise, 2008-05-27; 08-0527-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    Graduate students Everett Meyer, in the School of Medicine, and Bryan Bai, in the School of Engineering, have invented a system that emits sounds from small speakers intended for mounting to the exterior of hybrid vehicles. Their PANDA system, Meyer said, is about 5 decibels quieter than a regular combustion engine from the front and 10 to 20 decibels quieter from the back. (PANDA stands for "Pedestrian Awareness Noise-emitting Device and Application.)
  - Madeline Albright Speech / Sagan, 2008-05-27; 08-0527-2a; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
    In a conversation with Scott Sagan, former Secretary of State Madeleine Albright discussed a wide range of international conflicts facing the next president, as well as her experience as a high-powered woman in politics. The Stanford in Government and ASSU Speakers Bureau's choice this year for "Big Speaker," Albright addressed a packed audience during the event in Kresge Auditorium.
  - Madeline Albright Q & A, 2008-05-27; 08-0527-2b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 53)
  - Madeline Albright, Cutaways, 2008-05-27; 08-0527-3; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
  - René Girard Interview & Cutaways, 2008-06-04; 08-0604-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    René Girard, the Andrew B. Hammond Professor of French Language, Literature and Civilization, Emeritus, and member of the venerable Académie française, talks to Stanford News Service writer Cynthia Haven about imitation, conflict and scapegoats.
  - Zuri Ray-Alladice 2008 Gunn High School Graduation, 2008-06-11; 08-0611-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    Zuri Ray Alladice, daughter of Stanford News Service Director Elaine Ray at her graduation from Gunn High school in 2008.
  - John Hennessy- Office working - Read & Sign Letters, Computer, 2008-06-13; 08-0613-1; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 51)
    [It appears to be generic footage of President John Hennessy in his office]
  - 2008 Commencement Part 3: Kirby Bumpus, 2008-06-15; 08-0615-2b; 1 videotape(s) (MiniDV) (Box 50)